{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Post-Construction Cleaning Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/40007/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40007,"taskName":"Post Construction - Clean-up","taskDescription":"Clean Up Job-site after Construction","xmTaskDescriptor":"Post-Construction Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":50,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Post-Construction construction job cleaner commercial","textMessagingName":"Cln Post-Construct","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically done by professional cleaners after the work crews are finished with their work \u0026 before the residents start using the new or renewed spaces.","rolloverShortDesc":"Thorough post-construction clean up.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean Up Job-site after Construction.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Post-Construction Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Construction Site Cleanup","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Post Construction Clean-up","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Post Construction - Clean-up","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Post-Construction Clean-up Project","urlName":"Post-Construction-Clean-up","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Construction Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Post-Construction, construction, job, cleaner, commercial, removal, clean, dirt, contruction, Cleanup, after, up, site","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":331,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40007/":{"taskOID":40007,"originalTaskOID":40007,"setID":331,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1556,"questionDisplayText":"Types of Construction Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of construction work are you having done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3715,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Major new construction (walls and structural elements moved and built)","answerDisplayText":"Major new construction (walls and structural elements moved and built)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel or addition (carpentry, drywall, cabinets, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Remodel or addition (carpentry, drywall, cabinets, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4563,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Painting or staining","answerDisplayText":"Painting or staining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5097,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Reflooring or installing/refinishing wood floors","answerDisplayText":"Reflooring or installing/refinishing wood floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5816,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Small projects","answerDisplayText":"Small projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":783,"questionDisplayText":"Items to be Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the items in your home that need dusting and cleaning. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6779,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls, ceiling, woodwork","answerDisplayText":"Walls, ceiling, woodwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1259,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Carpeting","answerDisplayText":"Carpeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6366,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile, vinyl, or linoleum","answerDisplayText":"Tile, vinyl, or linoleum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2929,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hardwood flooring","answerDisplayText":"Hardwood flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3865,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Mirrors","answerDisplayText":"Mirrors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3582,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Light fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Light fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1661,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Counters, cabinets, and shelving","answerDisplayText":"Counters, cabinets, and shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":715,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Air ducts","answerDisplayText":"Air ducts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":782,"questionDisplayText":"Windows Cleaned Inside and Out","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want the windows cleaned, inside and out?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1556,"questionDisplayText":"Types of Construction Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of construction work are you having done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3715,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Major new construction (walls and structural elements moved and built)","answerDisplayText":"Major new construction (walls and structural elements moved and built)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel or addition (carpentry, drywall, cabinets, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Remodel or addition (carpentry, drywall, cabinets, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4563,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Painting or staining","answerDisplayText":"Painting or staining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5097,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Reflooring or installing/refinishing wood floors","answerDisplayText":"Reflooring or installing/refinishing wood floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5816,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Small projects","answerDisplayText":"Small projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3715,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Major new construction (walls and structural elements moved and built)","answerDisplayText":"Major new construction (walls and structural elements moved and built)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel or addition (carpentry, drywall, cabinets, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Remodel or addition (carpentry, drywall, cabinets, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4563,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Painting or staining","answerDisplayText":"Painting or staining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5097,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Reflooring or installing/refinishing wood floors","answerDisplayText":"Reflooring or installing/refinishing wood floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5816,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Small projects","answerDisplayText":"Small projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":783,"questionDisplayText":"Items to be Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the items in your home that need dusting and cleaning. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6779,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls, ceiling, woodwork","answerDisplayText":"Walls, ceiling, woodwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1259,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Carpeting","answerDisplayText":"Carpeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6366,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile, vinyl, or linoleum","answerDisplayText":"Tile, vinyl, or linoleum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2929,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hardwood flooring","answerDisplayText":"Hardwood flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3865,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Mirrors","answerDisplayText":"Mirrors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3582,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Light fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Light fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1661,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Counters, cabinets, and shelving","answerDisplayText":"Counters, cabinets, and shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":715,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Air ducts","answerDisplayText":"Air ducts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6779,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls, ceiling, woodwork","answerDisplayText":"Walls, ceiling, woodwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1259,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Carpeting","answerDisplayText":"Carpeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6366,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile, vinyl, or linoleum","answerDisplayText":"Tile, vinyl, or linoleum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2929,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hardwood flooring","answerDisplayText":"Hardwood flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3865,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Mirrors","answerDisplayText":"Mirrors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3582,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Light fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Light fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1661,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Counters, cabinets, and shelving","answerDisplayText":"Counters, cabinets, and shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":715,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Air ducts","answerDisplayText":"Air ducts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":782,"questionDisplayText":"Windows Cleaned Inside and Out","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want the windows cleaned, inside and out?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}